Music
It was just two levels, sitting in the car, listening to the blonde falling for each other
Picking on skies, feeling super childish, no Donald Glovel
We score for my mother, like where you at tonight, I know I love her, I was all alone
With the love of my life, she's got glitter for skin, my Brady and baby in the night
I don't need no light to see you shine
It's your golden honor, you're so down to earth
We were just two levels, feet upon the dash, driving over fast, burning through the summer
Brady won't blouse, make the moment last, she got solar power, minutes feel like I was
She knew she was about to skin you, even imagine falling like I did for the love of my life
She's got blown her face, so glorious looking at eyes, my angel light
I was all alone with the love of my life, she's got glitter for skin, my Brady and baby in the night
I don't need no light to see you shine
It's your golden honor, you're so down to earth
you